Uptime is usually measured as a percentage of time that assistance is available.
正常运行时间通常以可用时间的百分比来衡量
99.9 percent is a standard uptime provided by many Service Level Agreements or SLAs.
99.9% 是许多服务级别协议或 SLA 提供的标准正常运行时间
This means that your service should be up and running normally 99.9 percent of the time,
这意味着您的服务应该正常运行并正常运行 99.9% 的时间
typically measured over the course of a month.
通常是在一个月内测得的
You will agree on this metric with your customers.
您将与客户商定该指标
You are attesting to the fact that you can keep
你在证明你能保持
your platform available that percentage of the time,
你的平台占了时间的百分比
and your customer finds that amount of time to be acceptable.
您的客户会发现您可以接受的时间量
Depending on your product and industry,
根据您的产品和行业
your SLA may define a higher or lower uptime.
您的 SLA 可能定义较高或更低的正常运行时间
You will also likely face penalties if you do not achieve your uptime commitment.
如果您不履行您的正常工作时间承诺 您也可能面临处罚
This usually comes in the form of
这通常以
monetary or service credits that you would owe your customers.
您将欠客户的货币或服务积分
Meeting your SLA requires diligence.
满足您的 SLA 需要注意
You will need to track your platforms uptime so that you can
您需要跟踪平台正常运行时间 以便您可以
demonstrate to your customers that you are measuring it and meeting commitments.
向您的客户演示您正在测量它并履行承诺
In order to maintain a high level of uptime,
为了维持高水平的 uptime
you need to have redundancy throughout your service.
您需要在整个服务中具有冗余
Uptime is usually referred to as a number of nines.
Uptime 通常称为多个 n
For example, an SLA of 99.9 percent is referred to as having three nines of availability.
例如  99.9% 的 SLA 被称为具有三种可用性
You will also hear terms such as three and a half nines.
你也会听到三个半的词
This would mean 99.95 percent uptime.
这将意味着 99.95% 的正常运行时间
To reach a moderate level of uptime,
要达到中等水平的 uptime
you cannot have a single point of failure.
你就不能有单一的失败点
A single point of failure is any one component that were it to fail,
唯一的失败点是任何一个失败的成分
would take down a system until it were repaired or replaced.
将会对系统进行修复或更换
Any single point of failure will,
任何单一的失败点
at some point, fail.
有些时候失败了
You could call this Murphy's law,
你可以称之为墨菲定律
but really it's just probability, everything fails eventually.
但这只是概率事件最终都失败了
When this happens, the time required to recover will likely cause you to miss your SLA.
发生这种情况时 恢复所需的时间很可能会导致您错过 SLA
Be thoughtful of all the things that need to be redundant;
要考虑所有需要冗余的东西 ;
databases, networking, servers, caches,
数据库 网络 服务器 高速缓存
also staff, people who know how to fix things and not just one
也是工作人员 懂得修东西的人 不只是一个
person because people go on vacation or sleep through emergency pager alerts.
因为人们通过紧急寻呼机警报来度假或睡觉